Please give me one best for us to welcome to Miss Amanda DeVos.
Y'all good?
Good.
All right.
I got 40 MCs on my block, walking with a block, claiming that they real hip-hop.
80 feet in Timbs and sagging jeans, rhyming about cream, chasing the same dream.
This poem is a little ditty, but the 40 MCs on what seems like every block in New York City.
It's a pity you won't say rhyming for the love, it's for the fame, treating this culture
like it's a game.
See, their mental state is getting minds when they script between the lines.
They ain't worried about the rhyme, they just trying to make a dime.
So in time, the hosts are pushing pens to get them arranged, like milk past the date, go
quickly down the drain.
There was 40 MCs on my block, and three head kids.
One got shot, four got knocked.
One got with a chick that made him put his pad away, the other went back to school to
get her BFA.
Now, I'm a rapper, they all say, till their pockets ain't getting sucked, or their lives
get a little rough.
Man, that MC shit was just a bluff, because when the going got tough, it didn't take much
for the MCs to get hushed.
So now there's 30 MCs on my block, holding down the cypher spot in front of the corner shop,
60 arms swinging as they frantically fold, feeding them to spit some shit to make their poetry
go, oh, but you know how they go.
I'm that nigga, they all figure, wannabe digger, screaming, soon I'll be making major figures.
They start rhyming for the money, because they think it's easy, but insincerity has no longevity.
You feel me?
Eventually, three got locked up, four got a weed spot in a four-floor walk-up, five had
kids, two got knocked up.
Three was living with they moms, and fours act like grown-ups had to go get jobs, so they
hung the mic up.
One became a born-again Christian.
And when cats ask him, yo, when you gon' rhyme again, he looks up and says, ask him.
So now there's 10 MCs on my block, but the rest will be replaced before this show is done,
ready with their bullshit raps to rape this culture and run.
Because there's so many fake MCs who are whack, about 40 on every block, in every city
to be exact.
But rhyming words with nouns and verbs doesn't make you an MC.
You gotta live for the funk and die for the funk.
If you don't, put your pen down, please.